<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>SPARC FAIR Codeathon 2022 on SPARC FAIR Codeathon</title><link>https://quilted-tutorial.github.io/SPARC-guru/</link><description>Recent content in SPARC FAIR Codeathon 2022 on SPARC FAIR Codeathon</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://quilted-tutorial.github.io/SPARC-guru/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>https://quilted-tutorial.github.io/SPARC-guru/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://quilted-tutorial.github.io/SPARC-guru/about/</guid><description>The Stimulating Peripheral Activity to Relieve Conditions (SPARC) program is supported by the NIH Common Fund to provide a scientific and technological foundation for future bioelectronic medicine devices and protocols. The initiative is made up of over 60 research teams scattered around the globe, all working together on a common objective. The entire project is Open Source and follows the Findable, Accessible, Interoperable, and Reusable (FAIR) guidelines for data management.</description></item><item><title>Getting started</title><link>https://quilted-tutorial.github.io/SPARC-guru/getting_started/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://quilted-tutorial.github.io/SPARC-guru/getting_started/</guid><description>Initial setup If you have not already done so, clone the GitHub repository onto your local machine into the SPARC-tutorial folder with the following command:
$ git clone git@github.com:SPARC-FAIR-Codeathon/SPARC-Tutorial.git SPARC-tutorial The tutorial is contained in a Jupyter Notebook and requires JupyterLab to run.
If you are familiar with JupyterLab Open JupyterLab and navigate to the SPARC-tutorial folder. Select the tutorial you want to try and enter the corresponding folder. Open the SPARC-tutorial.</description></item><item><title>Meet the team</title><link>https://quilted-tutorial.github.io/SPARC-guru/team/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://quilted-tutorial.github.io/SPARC-guru/team/</guid><description>Our team is based in Auckland, New Zealand at the Auckland Bioengineering Institute.
Yuda Munarko (Team Leader) Omkar Athavale (Doc Writer and Tutorial Developer) Mathias Roesler (Doc Writer and Web Developer) Niloofar Shahidi (Article Writer and Design Artist) Kenneth Tran (Doc Writer and Tutorial Developer)</description></item><item><title>Tutorial 1: Mapping 2D data points to a 3D organ scaffold</title><link>https://quilted-tutorial.github.io/SPARC-guru/post/tutorial-1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://quilted-tutorial.github.io/SPARC-guru/post/tutorial-1/</guid><description>Before you start Please make sure you have followed the instruction in the Getting started page before selecting your tutorial.
Mapping 2D data points to a 3D organ scaffold The first Quilted Tutorial consists in mapping 2D data point to a 3D scaffold. It has been tested using Ubuntu 22.04 LTS and Python 3.10.4
In your terminal, navigate to the tutorial-1 folder in the cloned directory and start JupyterLab:
$ cd SPARC-tutorial/tutorial-1 &amp;amp;&amp;amp; jupyter-lab --LabApp.</description></item><item><title>Tutorial 2: Resampling dataset for simulations</title><link>https://quilted-tutorial.github.io/SPARC-guru/post/tutorial-2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://quilted-tutorial.github.io/SPARC-guru/post/tutorial-2/</guid><description>Before you start Please make sure you have followed the instruction in the Getting started page before selecting your tutorial.
Resampling dataset for simulations The second Quilted Tutorial consists in resampling some 2D data to prepare for simulations. It has been tested using Ubuntu 22.04 LTS and Python 3.10.4
In your terminal, navigate to the tutorial-2 folder in the cloned directory and start JupyterLab:
$ cd SPARC-tutorial/tutorial-2 &amp;amp;&amp;amp; jupyter-lab --LabApp.token='' --no-browser Follow this link to get started and open the SPARC-tutorial.</description></item></channel></rss>